Guide to the Robert A. M. Stern Architects Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project records for 1984, Accession 2009-M-066
  - Boyd/Smith, Lexington [The Hamptons], 1985-1987
    - Publicity materials (Box 15)
    - Construction drawings (Box 44–45)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 44–46)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 44–45)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 58)
    - Photographs (Box 66)
    - Slides (Box 63, Box 66)
  - Reiss House, 1984
    Job number: 84240
    - Job files (Box 16)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 47)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 59)
    - Photographs (Box 66)
    - Slides (Box 66)
  - Ashkin House, 1984-1988
    Job number: 84241
    Job location: Hewlitt Harbor, NY
    - Correspondence (Box 16–18)
    - Job files (Box 16–18)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 48)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 48)
    - Construction drawings (Box 47–48)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 47)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 48)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 47)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 18, Box 59)
    - Photographs (Box 67)
    - Slides (Box 63–64, Box 67)
  - Tegeler Hafen, 1985-1989
    Job number: 84242
    Job location: Berlin, Germany
    - Correspondence (Box 19)
    - Job files (Box 19)
    - Publicity materials (Box 19)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 48)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 48)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 48)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 19, Box 59)
    - Photographs (Box 67)
    - Slides (Box 64, Box 67)
  - Sherman Garden, 1984
    Job number: 84243
    Job location: Riverdale, NY
    - Photographs (Box 67)
  - Hillcrest Square, 1984-1985
    Job number: 84244
    Job location: San Diego, CA
    - Correspondence (Box 19–21)
    - Job files (Box 19–21)
    - Publicity materials (Box 21)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 49)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 49)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 49)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 21, Box 59)
    - Photographs (Box 67)
    - Slides (Box 64, Box 67)
  - Escondido Civic Center, 1984
    Job number: 84245
    Job location: Escondido, CA
    - Presentation drawings (Box 49)
    - Photographs (Box 67)
    - Slides (Box 67)
  - International House Auditorium, 1987
    Job number: 84246
    - Correspondence (Box 26)
    - Job files (Box 22–26)
    - Publicity materials (Box 25)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 50)
    - Construction drawings (Box 50)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 50)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 59)
    - Photographs (Box 67)
    - Slides (Box 64, Box 67)
  - East Hampton Industries Office, 1984
    Job number: 84247
    - Correspondence (Box 27)
    - Job files (Box 27)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 50)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 50)
  - Ember House and Poolhouse [Sunstone], 1984-1989
    Job number: 84248
    Job location: Quogue, NY
    - Correspondence (Box 27–28)
    - Job files (Box 27–28)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 51)
    - Construction drawings (Box 51)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 51)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 51)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 28, Box 59)
    - Photographs (Box 67)
    - Slides (Box 64–65, Box 67)
  - Amster House [Calf Creek], 1984-1987
    Job number: 84249
    Job location: Water Mill, NY
    - Correspondence (Box 29, Box 32)
    - Job files (Box 29–32)
    - Publicity materials (Box 31)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 53)
    - Construction drawings (Box 52)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 53)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 60–61)
    - Photographs (Box 67)
    - Slides (Box 65, Box 67)
  - Colfax Development House: Lot 8, 1983-1989
    Job number: 84252
    Job location: Skillman, NJ
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 54)
    - Construction drawings (Box 54)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 54)
    - Slides (Box 65)
  - Mecox Fields: Lot 1: Gans House, 1984
    Job number: 84253
    - Construction drawings (Box 54)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 54)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 61)
    - Photographs (Box 67)
    - Slides (Box 65, Box 67)
  - Appignani Apartment, 1984-1985
    Job number: 84255
    - Job files (Box 32)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 54)
    - Construction drawings (Box 54)
    - Slides (Box 65)
  - Weiss Residence, 1984
    Job number: 84257
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 61)
    - Slides (Box 65)
  - Catlin House renovation, 1984-1985
    Job number: 84258
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 54)
    - Construction drawings (Box 54)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 61)
    - Slides (Box 65)
  - Preakness Hills Country Club, 1984-1985
    Job number: 84262
    Job location: Wayne, NJ
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 55)
    - Construction drawings (Box 55)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 55)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 61)
    - Slides (Box 65)
  - Pitkin Bargain Center, 1984
    Job number: 84263
    - Photographs (Box 65)
    - Slides (Box 65)
  - McGee Farm, 1984-1985
    Job number: 84265
    Job location: Holmdel, NJ
    - Correspondence (Box 32)
    - Job files (Box 32)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 55)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 55)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 55)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 61)
    - Photographs (Box 67)
    - Slides (Box 65, Box 67)
- Project records for 1980-1983, Accession 2007-M-094
  - Modern Architecture After Modernism Pavilion, 1980
    Job number: 80106
    Job location: Linz, Austria
    - Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Job files (Box 2)
    - Construction drawings (Box 108)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 94)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 94)
    - Framed artwork (Folder 1A)
  - Chicago Tribune competition, late entry, 1980-1983
    Job number: 80107
    - Correspondence (Box 2)
    - Job files (Box 2)
    - Publicity materials (Box 2)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 108)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 108)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 2)
    - Photographs (Box 2)
  - Venice Biennale Façade, Strada Novissima, 1980
    Job number: 80108
    Job location: Venice, Italy
    - Correspondence (Box 2–3)
    - Job files (Box 2–3)
    - Publicity materials (Box 2–3)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 108)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 94)
    - Models (Box 187)
    - Photographs (Box 2)
    - Framed artwork (Folder 1B)
  - Visitor's Center, 1979-1980
    Job number: 80109
    Job location: Shaker Village, KY
    - Correspondence (Box 3)
    - Job files (Box 3)
    - Publicity materials (Box 3)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 108)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 108)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 94)
  - Walker Medical Suite, 1980
    Job number: 80110
    - Correspondence (Box 3, Box 7)
    - Job files (Box 3, Box 7)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 108)
    - Construction drawings (Box 108)
    - Lighting drawings (Box 94)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 94)
  - Knoll Table, 1980
    Job number: 80111
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 109)
  - Nanco Offices, 1979-1980
    Job number: 80112
    - Correspondence (Box 7)
    - Job files (Box 7)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 109)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 94, Box 109)
    - Construction drawings (Box 109)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 94)
  - Capasso Apartment, 1980-1982
    Job number: 80113
    - Correspondence (Box 4, Box 7)
    - Job files (Box 4, Box 7)
    - Publicity materials (Box 4)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 111)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 94, Box 110–111)
    - Construction drawings (Box 110)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 111)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 4, Box 94)
  - Subway Suburb, 1980
    Job number: 80114
    - Framed artwork (Folder 1B)
  - Crecco Apartment, 1980-1981
    Job number: 80115
    - Correspondence (Box 4)
    - Job files (Box 4)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 4)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 111)
  - Columbia University: Ferris Booth Hall renovation, 1980-1981
    Job number: 80117
    - Correspondence (Box 4–5)
    - Job files (Box 4–5)
    - Publicity materials (Box 5)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 94, Box 112)
    - Construction drawings (Box 112)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 112)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 5, Box 94)
  - Texas Toilets [Toilet Museum], 1981
    Job number: 80118
    Job location: Houston, TX
    - Correspondence (Box 5)
    - Construction drawings (Box 112)
  - City Hall Annex competition, 1980
    Job number: 80120
    Job location: Cincinnati, OH
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 94)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 5)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 94)
  - Hines-Griefen House, 1980-1981
    Job number: 80121
    Job location: Farm Neck, Martha's Vineyard, MA
    - Correspondence (Box 5–6)
    - Job files (Box 5–6)
    - Publicity materials (Box 6)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 113)
    - Construction drawings (Box 113)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 113)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 6, Box 94)
  - "Scaling Modernism" [statue, collaboration with Robert Graham], 1980
    Job number: 80122
    - Correspondence (Box 8)
    - Job files (Box 8)
    - Publicity materials (Box 8)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 113)
  - Liebowitz Apartment, 1980-1982
    Job number: 80123
    - Correspondence (Box 8)
    - Job files (Box 8)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 8)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 94, Box 114)
    - Construction drawings (Box 114)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 94)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 114)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 8, Box 94)
  - D. O. M. Corporation Headquarters competition, 1980
    Job number: 80124
    Job location: Bruhl, Germany
    - Correspondence (Box 9)
    - Job files (Box 9)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 114)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 94)
    - Framed artwork (Folder 1C)
  - Garibaldi Meucci Museum competition, 1980-1982
    Job number: 80125
    - Job files (Box 9)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 114)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 94)
  - Meltzer Apartment, 1980
    Job number: 80126
    - Correspondence (Box 9)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 9, Box 114)
  - Wolfer Residence renovations, 1980-1983
    Job number: 80127
    - Job files (Box 9)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 115)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 115)
    - Construction drawings (Box 115)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 94, Box 115)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 115)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 115)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 94)
  - Bozzi Residence and Pool House, 1980-1983
    Job number: 80128
    - Correspondence (Box 9)
    - Job files (Box 9)
    - Publicity materials (Box 9)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 9)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 116)
    - Construction drawings (Box 116)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 116)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 116)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 9, Box 95)
  - Keith House I, 1980-1981
    Job number: 80129
    Job location: Locust Valley, NY
    - Job files (Box 10)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 117)
    - Construction drawings (Box 117)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 117)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 117)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 95)
  - Bourke House Dressing Rooms, 1981
    Job number: 80130
    - Correspondence (Box 10)
    - Job files (Box 10)
    - Construction drawings (Box 117)
  - Patricof House renovations, 1981
    Job number: 80131
    - Correspondence (Box 10–11)
    - Job files (Box 10–11)
    - Publicity materials (Box 11)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 11, Box 118)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 118)
    - Construction drawings (Box 118)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 118)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 95)
  - Catlin and Cox Offices, 1980
    Job number: 80132
    - Correspondence (Box 11)
    - Job files (Box 11)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 118)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 118)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 11, Box 95)
  - San Juan Capistrano Library competition, 1980
    Job number: 81033
    Job location: San Juan Capistrano, CA
    - Correspondence (Box 11)
    - Job files (Box 11)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 118)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 118)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 118)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 95)
  - Ackerman Apartment, 1980
    Job number: 80134
    - Correspondence (Box 11–12)
    - Job files (Box 11–12)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 11)
    - Construction drawings (Box 119)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 119)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 119)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 12, Box 95)
  - Cove Hollow Farm Lot 10: Peters House [House for Corbel Properties], 1980-1981
    Job number: 80135
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 119)
    - Construction drawings (Box 119)
  - Capasso Poolhouse, 1980-1983
    Job number: 80288
    Job location: Westhampton, NY
    - Job files (Box 12)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 95, Box 120)
    - Construction drawings (Box 120)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 120)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 120)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 95)
  - Newhouse Apartment renovation, 1980
    Job number: 80289
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 119)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 119)
  - Catlin Residence, 1980-1982
    Job number: 80298
    - Correspondence (Box 12)
    - Job files (Box 12)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 120)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 120)
  - Young-Hoffman Gallery Exhibition, 1980-1981
    Job number: 81137
    - Job files (Box 12)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 121)
  - Woods Residence, 1981-1982
    Job number: 81138
    Job location: New Canaan, CT
    - Correspondence (Box 12)
    - Job files (Box 12)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 121)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 121)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 95)
  - Richmond Centre Urban Design Study, 1981
    Job number: 81139
    Job location: Richmond, VA
    - Presentation drawings (Box 121)
  - Cove Hollow Farm Lot 10: Shapiro House [House for Corbel Properties], 1980-1981
    Job number: 81140
    - Correspondence (Box 13)
    - Job files (Box 13)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 121)
    - Construction drawings (Box 121)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 121)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 121)
  - Roizen House, 1980
    Job number: 81141
    Job location: Shelter Island, NY
    - Correspondence (Box 13)
    - Job files (Box 13)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 122)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 122)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 95)
  - Stone Douglass House, 1981
    Job number: 81143
    - Correspondence (Box 13)
    - Job files (Box 13)
    - Publicity materials (Box 13)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 13)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 122)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 122)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 95)
  - Robert Douglass Residence, 1981
    Job number: 81144
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 122)
  - Keith House II, 1981-1982
    Job number: 81145
    Job location: Mill Neck, NY
    - Correspondence (Box 14)
    - Job files (Box 14)
    - Publicity materials (Box 14)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 123)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 123)
    - Construction drawings (Box 123)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 95)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 123)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 123)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 95)
  - Cove Hollow Farm: Shapiro Group Houses, 1981
    Job number: 81146
    - Presentation drawings (Box 124)
  - Offices for Obstetric and Gynecologic Associates, 1981-1982
    Job number: 81147
    - Correspondence (Box 15)
    - Job files (Box 15)
    - Publicity materials (Box 15)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 15, Box 124)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 124)
    - Construction drawings (Box 124)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 124)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 95)
  - Mecox Fields: Preliminary Design and Planning, 1981-1988
    Job number: 81148
    - Correspondence (Box 15)
    - Job files (Box 15)
    - Publicity materials (Box 15)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 125)
    - Construction drawings (Box 125)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 125)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 15, Box 95)
  - Stuart House, 1981-1983
    Job number: 81149
    - Correspondence (Box 16)
    - Job files (Box 16)
  - Lincoln Squash Club, 1981
    Job number: 81150
    - Correspondence (Box 16)
    - Job files (Box 16)
    - Publicity materials (Box 16)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 126)
    - Construction drawings (Box 126)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 126)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 95)
  - Stratford at North Hills, 1981
    Job number: 81293
    Job location: North Hills, NY
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 127)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 95)
  - Little Red School House alterations, 1982
    Job number: 81294
    - Job files (Box 16)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 127)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 127)
  - Stuart Townhouse, 1980-1983
    Job number: 81295
    - Correspondence (Box 16)
    - Job files (Box 16)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 95)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 95)
  - Roberts Apartment, 1981-1982
    Job number: 81297
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 127)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 127)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 95)
  - Edwin Stern Apartment, 1981-1982
    Job number: 82150
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 127)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 96)
  - Patricof Apartment, 1981
    Job number: 82151
    - Job files (Box 17)
  - Meltzer Apartment, 1982
    Job number: 82152
    Job location: Dallas, TX
    - Job files (Box 17)
  - Archdeacon Development Houses, 1981-1982
    Job number: 82153
    Job location: Aspen, CO
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 128)
    - Construction drawings (Box 128)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 128)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 128)
  - Shaw-Walker Showroom, 1981-1982
    Job number: 82154
    - Correspondence (Box 17–18)
    - Job files (Box 17–18)
    - Publicity materials (Box 18)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 17)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 128)
    - Construction drawings (Box 128)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 128)
    - Lighting drawings (Box 128)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 18, Box 96)
  - Millstein House, 1981
    Job number: 82155
    Job location: Napeague, NY
    - Correspondence (Box 18)
    - Job files (Box 18)
    - Publicity materials (Box 18)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 129)
    - Construction drawings (Box 129)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 129)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 96)
  - Kalamazoo Center Urban Design competition, 1981
    Job number: 82156
    Job location: Kalamazoo, MI
    - Job files (Box 18)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 129)
  - Raymond Hood exhibit at the Institute for Architecture and Urban Studies, 1981
    Job number: 82157
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 129)
  - Rothschild Apartment, 1981-1983
    Job number: 82158
    - Correspondence (Box 19–20)
    - Job files (Box 19–20)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 130)
    - Construction drawings (Box 130)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 130)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 130)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 20, Box 96)
  - "Classical Corner", House and Garden magazine, 1982
    Job number: 82159
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 130)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 96)
  - Shaw-Walker furniture design, 1982
    Job number: 82161
    Job location: Muskegon, MI
    - Correspondence (Box 21)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 131)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 96)
  - Shaw-Walker Showroom, 1982-1983
    Job number: 82162
    - Correspondence (Box 21)
    - Job files (Box 21)
    - Publicity materials (Box 21)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 131)
    - Construction drawings (Box 131)
    - Lighting drawings (Box 131)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 131)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 96)
  - University of Virginia: Sprigg Lane Dormitory, 1982-1984
    Job number: 82163
    Job location: Charlottesville, VA
    - Correspondence (Box 22)
    - Job files (Box 22)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 132)
    - Construction drawings (Box 132)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 132)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 96)
    - Photographs (Box 22)
  - University of Virginia: Observatory Hill Dining Hall, 1982-1984
    Job number: 82164
    - Correspondence (Box 23)
    - Job files (Box 23)
    - Publicity materials (Box 23)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 133)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 133)
    - Construction drawings (Box 133)
    - Lighting drawings (Box 133)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 133)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 96)
    - Framed artwork (Folder 1C)
  - St. Andrews: Condominiums, Gate House, Pump House, 1982-1986
    Job number: 82165
    - Correspondence (Box 26–30)
    - Job files (Box 24–30)
    - Publicity materials (Box 30)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 140)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 137–138, Box 140–141)
    - Construction drawings (Box 134–137, Box 139)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 140)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 138–139)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 30, Box 96)
    - Photographs (Box 30)
  - Ondine IV Yacht interiors, 1982-1983
    Job number: 82166
    - Correspondence (Box 31)
    - Job files (Box 31)
    - Publicity materials (Box 31)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 142)
    - Construction drawings (Box 142)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 96)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 31, Box 96)
  - University of Virginia: Faulkner House Apartment project competition, 1982
    Job number: 82167
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 142)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 142)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 96)
  - Anthony Fisher Residence, 1982
    Job number: 82168
    - Correspondence (Box 32)
    - Job files (Box 32)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 143)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 143)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 96)
  - Millstein House renovation, 1982
    Job number: 82169
    Job location: Amagansett, NY
    - Correspondence (Box 32)
    - Job files (Box 32)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 143)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 143)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 96)
  - Shaw-Walker Showroom, Pacific Design Center, 1982
    Job number: 82170
    - Correspondence (Box 32)
    - Job files (Box 32)
    - Publicity materials (Box 32)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 143)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 143)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 97)
  - Dushey House, 1982-1984
    Job number: 82171
    - Correspondence (Box 32)
    - Job files (Box 32)
    - Publicity materials (Box 32)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 144)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 145)
    - Construction drawings (Box 144–145)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 145)